(Penny:)The Brady Bunch.
(Raj:)Okay.
"Sammy Hagar replaced David Lee Roth
as the lead singer in what group?"
(Sheldon(after they look at each other in confusion):)The Brady Bunch?
(Penny:)Van Halen.
All right. "Madonna was married
to this Ridgemont High alum."
(Penny:)Oh, my God. Sean Penn.
(Leonard:)How do you know these things?
(Penny:)I go outside and I talk to people.
Okay, here.
"What actor holds the record...
(Penny:)...for being named People magazine's
Sexiest Man Alive?"
- William Shatner.
- Wait.
(Leonard:)I don't think it's Shatner.
Then it's gotta be Patrick Stewart.
(Raj:)- No.
- Formal protest.
All right. "Singer who sang
'Oops!... I Did It Again'?"
(Raj:)Okay.
"Tweety bird thought he saw a what?"
(Sheldon(after they pass a smug look between each other):)Romulan.
Yes. He thought he saw a Romulan.
[PENNY SIGHS]